(Raj:)I'm not pouting, I'm brooding.
(Raj:)Which is how sexy men pout.
(Amy:)It actually was kind of fun.
(Raj:)You're just saying that.
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Bernadette:)I liked the time travel element.
(Raj:)Thank you.
I thought it was inspired.
(Leonard:)It was. By Terminator.
(Bernadette:)Well, I hope 20 years from now,
we really are all still together
(Bernadette:)and still friends.
(Penny:)-Definitely.
-Of course.
Hey, how about this?
Whether we're friends, not friends,
scattered around the world,
no matter what,
let's all promise to meet
in front of this building
exactly 20 years
from tonight at 8:00 p.m.
And have dinner
like we always do.
Aw, I love it.
(Leonard:)Putting it in my phone right now.
(Penny:)Yeah, me, too.
(Stuart:)My phone doesn't have a calendar.
It's all right,
I'll just write it on my hand.
(Raj:)And it's done.
(Penny:)Yup, we're all in.
(Bernadette:)All right,
I'll see you guys in 20 years.
(Stuart:)I knew it.